<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DEFLECTION ARMOR.com]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DEFLECTION ARMOR.com]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 03:10:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome</h1><p>Welcome to our new web site!</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/welcome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43c31fe5-b07d-4992-9fc9-b364094f4019</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 18:57:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>“The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu” —Chris Cord Fantastic martial arts are taught there. Not for everybody, if you can’t behave in kids class they won’t train you. Good for them having standards and sticking with them. Same thing in adult classes if you’re a thug or a jerk they ask you not to train, which is great for those of us that want to train with good fun people. Some people might think they are elitists, but since they are the best school that I have trained at they can afford to be. You can’t find a better school in my opinion. —Jen Fairbanks Both of our kids, a girl & boy, have been with Sensei Benson for nearly 10 years. They’ve moved from the kid’s classes to the adult classes and have enjoyed every minute. We “shopped around” at first, but no one came close to Sensei Benson’s approach and expectation for developing the “whole person.” “Kaizen” – or “continuous improvement” is more than a business name here. If you desire the self-discipline of body and mind that authentic martial arts is about, then you can learn it here. My kids developed excellent skills to the point that I worry much less about my daughter walking across her college campus. But my real thanks to Sensei is for their well-developed sense of constant awareness of their surroundings, personal confidence and the impact of their actions on those around them. I give Kaizen Martial Arts an A+++ —Wendy Adams If you’re looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be —JD Goodwin Best dojo ever…sometimes funny, always skilled instruction in a discipline that is still an art and hasn’t been watered down into a “sport”. —Daniel Hocker This Martial Arts Studio is the REAL deal! Forget Karate, Kung Fu or TaeKownDo, I’ll take a real Ninja master any day of the week. GREAT instruction, FAIR prices, FUN environment. —Christopher Lee</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/the-absolute-best-dojo-in-colorado-for-ninjutsu-and-jujutsu/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">13645d0d-28d7-42d3-b9b3-aa30168de8a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2015 03:09:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predator Armor]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Predator Armor</h1><p>The power of scenario based training is in providing the ability to overcome the negative effects of the adrenal fear rush that will occur in the stress of an actual assault and even in training.</p><img src="http://strongtowerprinciples.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/STP400-e1442023364493.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://strongtowerprinciples.com/?page_id=4144</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8dba8151-f5d8-4f6c-8e5d-eea2b590424f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Full Force Combat Body Protection  The FAST Defense Predator Armour™ is unique among all other commercially available body armor in that it safely allows absolute full force strikes to vulnerable areas on the attacker’s body, yet allows for free mobility to realistically simulate an aggressive attacker.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/full-force-combat-body-protection-the-fast-defense-predator/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">65c6ca30-bbfa-421a-b0d9-8a780dd8d881</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:27:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Over 3 Decades of Research and Development  This cutting edge armor has evolved from over 30 years of intensive R&D and literally hundreds of thousands of live scenarios with people from no training up to professional fighters and elite military and Law Enforcement personnel. The result is the perfect balance of freedom of movement, weight and comfort, with maximum protective ability unlike no other.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/deflection-armor-com/over-3-decades-of-research-and-development-this-cutting-edg/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02523fcb-1f46-476a-b767-e1bc534f2ae1</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:27:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>